RG 005, Office of the Governor Records
Governor Records, Office of the
- Series 4. Correspondence, 1811-1933
  - Military Correspondence, 1832-1882; 8.5 cubic feet
    - Incoming Letters
      - Samuel A. Foote, 1834 May 30-1835 April 22 (Box 84)
      - Henry W. Edwards, 1835 May 4-October 37, 1837 July 17 (Box 84)
      - Roger S. Baldwin, 1844 January 11-1846 April 26 (Box 84)
      - Isaac Toucey, 1846 May 7-1847 April 20 (Box 84)
      - Clark Bissel, 1847 May 22-1849 January 18 (Box 84)
      - Joseph Trumbull, 1849 June 13-1850 January 8 (Box 84)
      - Thomas Seymour (Box 84)
        - 1850 May 11-1851 September 26 (Box 84)
        - 1851 October 2-1853 October 4 (Box 84A)
      - Charles H. Pond, 1853 October 24-1854 May 2 (Box 84A)
      - Henry S. Dutton, 1854 May 12-1855 April 19 (Box 84A)
      - William T. Minor, 1855 May 3-1856 June 7 (Box 84A)
      - Alexander H. Holley, 1857 May 6-1858 April 29 (Box 84A)
      - William A. Buckingham (Box 84A)
        - 1848 May 1-1859 May (Box 84A)
        - 1859 June-1861 September (Box 85)
        - 1861 October-1862 October (Box 86)
        - 1862 November-1863 December (Box 87)
        - 1864 January-1864 November (Box 87A)
        - 1864 December-1865 December (Box 88)
        - U.S. Government general correspondence, 1861 November-1864 (Box 88)
        - War Department (Box 88A)
          - General correspondence, 1861-1866 (Box 88A)
          - Adjutant General (Box 88A)
            - 1864 (Box 88A)
            - 1864 (Box 89)
          - Provost Marshall, 1863-1864 (Box 89)
          - Quartermaster General (Box 89)
            - 1861-1862 June (Box 89)
            - 1862 July-1863 (Box 90)
        - State Adjutant General (Box 90)
          - Printed orders, 1861-1862 (Box 90)
          - 1861-1863 July (Box 90)
          - 1863 August-1865 March (Box 91)
          - 1865 April-December (Box 91A)
        - State Commissary General (Box 91A)
          - Rations, 1861 May (Box 91A)
          - Rations/Receipts, 1861 April-May (Box 91A)
          - Bills, 1861 April-June (Box 91A)
          - Orders/Contracts, 1861 April-May (Box 91A)
        - State Agents (Box 91A)
          - Reports (Box 91A)
            - 1862-1862 (Box 91A)
            - 1864-1865 May (Box 92)
            - 1865 June-1865 December (Box 93)
        - State Miscellaneous (Box 93)
          - Governors of other states, undated (Box 93)
          - Governor's Foot Guard, 1862-1864 (Box 93)
          - Town officials, 1862-1863 (Box 93)
          - Charges against Col. Pardee, 1864 June (Box 93)
          - Medical Board reports, 1861-1864 (Box 93)
          - Notes paid Treasury, 1864 January (Box 93)
          - Tender of money by bonds, 1861 (Box 93)
          - Imported arms account, 1861-1862 (Box 93)
          - Special session, 1862 (Box 94)
          - Printed circulars, 1865-1866, undated (Box 94)
          - Bonds to respond to a draft, 1862 (Box 94)
          - Telegrams, 1861-1862, 1865-1866 (Box 94)
  - Muster rolls of the Governor's Foot Guard, 1881-1889 (Box 95)
  - Applications for admission to military hospitals, 1873-1882 (Box 96-98)
- Series 5. Bond Registers, 1819-1899; T000005; .5 cubic feet
  - Transcripts of bonds executed by sheriffs and other officials., 1819-1899 (Box 60)
- Series 6. Applications, 1848-1880; T001307; 2 cubic feet
  - Applications for offices and promotions, 1861-1865 (Box 61)
  - Applications of chaplains, 1861-1863 (Box 62)
  - Applications of surgeons, 1862-1864 (Box 62)
  - Commissioner of Deeds, 1848-1880 (Box 62)
- Series 7. Miscellaneous Reports, 1860-1945; T001259; 6 cubic feet
  - 1860-1861, 1863-1864, 1879-1892 (Box 61)
  - 1893-1894 (Box 62)
  - 1895-1914 (Box 63)
  - 1915-1924 (Box 64)
  - 1925-1932 (Box 65)
  - 1933-1945 (Box 66)
- Series 10. Commitment Papers, 1828-1948
  - T001255, 10.5 cubic feet
    - General Assembly resolutions, 1829, 1830, 1833 (Box 99)
    - Abstracts of beneficiaries, deaf, dumb, and blind, 1830 (Box 99)
    - Incoming letters
      - Deaf & dumb
        - 1828-1849 (Box 99B)
        - 1850-1858 April (Box 99C)
      - Indigent & insane
        - 1842, 1843-1845 (Box 100A)
        - 1846-1849 May (Box 100B)
        - 1850 April-1853 March (Box 100C)
        - 1853 April-1855 December (Box 100D)
        - 1856 January-1858 April (Box 100E)
      - Blind, 1833-1858 June (Box 101)
      - Insane, 1858-1861 (Box 101A)
      - Deaf, dumb, blind, indigent, 1860-1862 (Box 101A)
    - Incoming letters
      - 1862-1869 (Box 102)
      - 1869-1876 (Box 103)
    - State beneficiaries, Executive Department, 1875-1876 (Box 103)
    - Beneficiaries at different institutions, undated (Box 103)
    - Papers, Deaf, dumb, and blind persons, 1860-1882 (Box 104)
    - Commitments to asylums other than Middletown, 1875-1878 (Box 104)
    - Returns from towns on indigent and pauper insane persons, 1871-1874 (Box 104)
    - Insane beneficiaries, 1879-1884 (Box 105)
    - Discharges
      Apparently commitment papers for persons who died or were discharged.
      - A-L, 1869-1878 (Box 106)
      - M-Z, 1869-1878 (Box 106)
    - Record of beneficiaries, circa 1855-1935; 2 volumes
  - T001254, 22.5 cubic feet
    - Commitments to Middletown, 1877-1921
      Arranged by case number.
      - 1-2753 (Box 109)
      - 2754-4535 (Box 110)
      - 4536-6017 (Box 111)
      - 6018-7580 (Box 112)
      - 7581-9203 (Box 113)
      - 9204-10796 (Box 114)
      - 19797-12189 (Box 115)
      - 12190-13397 (Box 116)
      - 13398-14619 (Box 117)
      - 14620-15859 (Box 118)
      - 15660-17407 (Box 119)
      - 17416-18802 (Box 120)
    - Commitments to Norwich, 1904-1921
      - 1-446 (Box 121)
      - 447-1824 (Box 122)
      - 1825-3149 (Box 123)
      - 3150-5903 (Box 124)
    - Commitments sent to other institutions, 1871-1949
      Years 1871-1875 arranged alphabetically. Years 1879-1948 arranged chronologically.
      - 1871-1898 (Box 125)
      - 1899-1919 (Box 126)
      - 1919-1931 (Box 127)
      - 1931-1948 (Box 128)
      - Mansfield Colony for Epileptics, 1914-1916 (Box 128)
        Arranged by case number, 1-140.
    - Commitments, 1916-1947
      - 1916-1929 (Box 129)
      - 1930-1935 May (Box 130)
      - 1935 June-1937 (Box 131)
      - Commitment correspondence, 1935 June-1937 (Box 131)
    - Monthly hospital reports, 1869-1921
      - 1869-1898 (Box 132)
      - 1899-1921 (Box 133)
- Series 11. Appointment registers, 1871-1978; T003185; 2.5 cubic feet
  - Appointments, 1871-1933 (Box 1)
    Board and Commissions are ordered alphabetically within the volume.
    Appointments listed chronologically for each board and commission.
    Date range of volume refers to dates of appointments.
    The last expiration date noted is 1942.
  - Railroad, Steamboat, Street & Electric R.R. Policemen, 1898-1937 (Box 1)
  - Appointments, Loose-leaf binder, 1900-1959 (Box 1)
    The last expiration date noted is 1965.
    The bulk of the entries are dated from the 1940s and 1950s.
    Contains text of statutes for each board and commission.
  - Governor's Appointments, Permanent Records, by William F. Siering, Governor's Executive Clerk, 1893-1977 (Box 2)
    The last expiration date noted is 1986.
    The bulk of the entries are dated from the 1950s to 1970s.
  - Executive Clerk's Journal, William F. Siering, 1955-1978 (Box 3)
    The bulk of the entries are dated from the 1970s.
- Series 12. Commissioner of Deeds, 1879-1949; T003186
  - Records of Connecticut Residents in other states, 1879-1949; 1 volume
- Series 13. Office of the Lieutenant Governor, 1991-1994
  - Eunice Groark, 1991-1994; 1995-027; 3 cubic feet
    - Correspondence
      - 1991 (Box 1)
      - 1992-1993 April (Box 2)
      - 1993 June-1994 (Box 3)
  - M. Jodi Rell, circa 1995-2004; 1995-114; 7 cubic feet
    - Records, circa 1995-2004
  - Michael Fedele, 2007-2010; 2011-099; 16 cubic feet
    - Records, 2007-2010
  - Nancy Wyman, 2011-2015; 2017-003; 20 cubic feet
    - Records, 2011-2015
- Series 14. Requisitions and Waivers of Extraditions, 1905-1993
  - Requisitions, 1905-1959
    - 1991-009, 3.5 cubic feet
      - Outgoing
        - 1905-1908 (Box 1)
        - 1909-1913 (Box 2)
        - 1914-1917 (Box 3)
        - 1917-1920 (Box 4)
    - 1998-029A, 1 cubic foot
      - Outgoing, 1921-1924 (Box 1)
    - T001243, 2 cubic feet
      - Incoming
        - 1923-1924 July (Box 137)
        - 1924 September-1925 September (Box 138)
        - 1925 October-1926 (Box 139)
      - Outgoing, 1924-1926 (Box 140)
    - 1991-033, 2 cubic feet
      - Outgoing
        - 1926-1928 (Box 5)
        - 1929-1930 (Box 6)
    - 1999-147, 3 cubic feet
      - Outgoing
        - 1930 (Box 1)
        - 1931 (Box 2)
        - 1932 (Box 3)
      - Incoming
        - 1930-1932 March (Box 4)
        - 1932 March-1933 (Box 5)
    - 2000-018, 2 cubic feet
      - Incoming and Outgoing
        - 1947-1949 (Box 78)
        - 1948-1959 (Box 80)
  - Extradition Files and Waivers of Extraditions, 1950-1993
    - T003132, 41 cubic feet
      - Extradition Files, 1950-1975
        - Brown-George (Box 1)
        - Georgulis-Godfrey (Box 2)
        - Goedicke-Gosselin (Box 3)
        - Goulart-Hanesack (Box 4)
        - Hancy-Heywrd (Box 5)
        - Hicks-Holman (Box 6)
        - Holt-Ingles (Box 7)
        - Iorio-Johnson (Box 8)
        - Johnson-Jones (Box 9)
        - Jones-Kennedy, William E. (Box 10)
        - Kennedy, William Floyd-King (Box 11)
        - Kohler-LaPointe (Box 12)
        - Larmond-Liggett (Box 13)
        - Little-Mackenzie, Daniel A. (Box 14)
        - Mackenzie, George-Marshall (Box 15)
        - Marshall-MxCall (Box 16)
        - McCarthy-McFadden (Box 17)
        - McFarlin-Mercado (Box 18)
        - Merced-Moir (Box 19)
        - Montgomery-Munn (Box 20)
        - Murchison-Ocacio (Box 21)
        - O'Connell-Paolino (Box 22)
        - Paquin-Perrier (Box 23)
        - Perrone-Poole (Box 24)
        - Porchedeau-Rand (Box 25)
        - Randolph-Richello (Box 26)
        - Richter-Rodkin (Box 27)
        - Rodriguez-Rossi (Box 28)
        - Rossignol-Santos (Box 29)
        - Sapero-Seale (Box 30)
        - Seaton-Simmons (Box 31)
        - Simms-Somma (Box 32)
        - Spanos-Swass (Box 33)
        - Szabo-Turner (Box 34)
        - Vellencourt-Weiss (Box 35)
        - Welch-Wilcoxsen (Box 36)
        - Wilkes-Yellitze (Box 37)
        - Young-Zottola (Box 38)
      - Extradition Files, 1975-1982
        - Abbot-Avis (Box 39)
        - Ayala-Bianco (Box 40)
        - Blair-Brooks (Box 41)
        - Brown-Capone (Box 42)
        - Carpenter-Coffman (Box 43)
        - Cohen-Creel (Box 44)
        - Crisafi-Dendy (Box 45)
        - Diaz-Fanchen (Box 46)
        - Fealey-Foss (Box 47)
        - Foster-Girardin (Box 48)
        - Gomez-Hart (Box 49)
        - Harvey-Howard (Box 50)
        - Hughley-Kemp (Box 51)
        - Klinger-Lorc (Box 52)
        - Lowman-Masterson (Box 53)
        - Mathews-Michaud (Box 54)
        - Middlebrook-Morrow (Box 55)
        - Motts-O'Connell (Box 56)
        - Ogman-Piplein (Box 57)
        - Pope-Rizzio (Box 58)
        - Roberson-Sanabria (Box 59)
        - Sanchez-Seymour (Box 60)
        - Shack-Smith, Carlton A. (Box 61)
        - Smith, Claude Samuel, Jr.-Spencer (Box 62)
        - Spring-Sullivan (Box 63)
        - Summa-Thibault (Box 64)
        - Thomas-Townsend (Box 65)
        - Trerotola-Tuttle (Box 66)
        - Tyson-Vrusho (Box 67)
        - Wachter-Wells (Box 68)
        - Wentworth-Williams, Robert (Box 69)
        - Williams, Shelley-Zaler (Box 70)
        - Zikusto-Zunno (Box 71)
      - Extradition Files, 1982-1986
        - Abels-Badessa (Box 72)
        - Bailey-Bradley (Box 73)
        - Braley-Carter (Box 74)
        - Cassidy-Cote (Box 75)
        - Cowette-Dubek (Box 76)
        - Durham-Gannon (Box 77)
        - Garner-Green (Box 78)
        - Griffen-Herbert (Box 79)
        - Herman-Kaba (Box 80)
        - Kachuk-Koufos (Box 81)
        - Krill-Mancinone (Box 82)
        - Mandell-McGurgan (Box 83)
        - McHugh-Mims (Box 84)
        - Minutelli-Nelson (Box 85)
        - Nocera-Providence (Box 86)
        - Rafael-Sanders (Box 87)
        - Santiago-Sweeney (Box 88)
        - Sweeney-Vandowski (Box 89)
        - Vega-Williams (Box 90)
        - Williams-Zavalko (Box 91)
      - Petitions Denied
        - Alston-Reilly (Box 92)
        - Robinson-Rosabal (Box 93)
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 93)
        - Extradition folder/Sample letter/Information (Box 93)
        - [Misc.] (Box 93)
        - Extradition correspondence, 1957-1967 (Box 93)
        - Extradition correspondence, 1953-1959 (Box 93)
        - Extradition Officials Conference, Tulsa, Oklahoma, 1967 (Box 93)
      - Waivers of Extradition
        - 1975-1976 (Box 94)
        - 1976-1979 (Box 95)
        - 1979-1980 (Box 96)
        - 1981-1982 (Box 97)
        - 1982 (Box 98)
    - 2005-038, 1 cubic foot
      - Waivers of Extradition
        - 1980-1986 (Box 1)
        - 1987-1993 (Box 2)
        - Correspondence, 1988, 1992 (Box 2)
        - Manual, undated (Box 2)
    - 2011-108, 29 cubic feet
      - Extradition Files, 1951-1981
        - A-Bai (Box 1)
        - Bak-Bend (Box 2)
        - Bene-Broc (Box 3)
        - Broo-Capp (Box 4)
        - Capr-Cla (Box 5)
        - Cle-Cul (Box 6)
        - Cum-Del (Box 7)
        - Dem-Dum (Box 8)
        - Dun-Fe (Box 9)
        - Fi-Gam (Box 10)
      - Extradition Files, 1975-1979
        - A-Bo (Box 11)
        - Br-C (Box 12)
        - D-Gl (Box 13)
        - Go-Jones, John (Box 14)
        - Jones, Joseph-Mon (Box 15)
        - Mou-Riv (Box 16)
      - Extradition Files, 1985-1987
        - A-H, 1985 (Box 17)
        - J-Sl, 1985 (Box 18)
        - St-W, 1985 (Box 19)
        - A-Cl, 1986 (Box 19)
        - Co-H, 1986 (Box 20)
        - I-O, 1986 (Box 21)
        - P-Sc, 1986 (Box 22)
        - Sh-Y, 1986 (Box 23)
        - A-C, 1987 (Box 24)
        - D-Ha, 1987 (Box 25)
        - He-M, 1987 (Box 26)
        - O-R, 1987 (Box 27)
        - S, 1987 (Box 28)
        - T-W, 1987 (Box 29)
- Subgroup 20. Frank B. Weeks, 1909-1911; 1.75 cubic feet
  - T001247
    - Outgoing letters, 1909 November-1910 December (Box 201)
    - Incoming letters
      - 1909 April-1910 January (Box 202)
      - 1910 January-December (Box 203)
      - 1911 January-1912 December (Box 204)
  - 2007-035
    - Incoming letters, 1908-1910 (Box 1)
      Detail listing with letters.
- Subgroup 21. Simeon A. Baldwin, 1911-1915; T001231; 11.75 cubic feet
  - Numerical files, 1911-1912
    - 1-10 (Box 205)
    - 11-40 (Box 206)
    - 41-95 (Box 207)
    - 96-140 (Box 208)
    - 141-198 (Box 209)
    - 199-220 (Box 210)
    - 221-239 (Box 211)
    - 240-270 (Box 212)
    - 271-295 (Box 213)
    - 296-329 (Box 214)
    - 330-358 (Box 215)
    - 359-400 (Box 216)
  - Alphabetical card index
    - 1911-1912
      - A-Q (Box 217)
      - R-Z (Box 218)
    - 1913-1914
      - A-C (Box 218)
      - D-Mi (Box 219)
      - Mo-Z (Box 220)
  - Numerical files, 1913-1914
    - 1-12 (Box 221)
    - 13-20 (Box 222)
    - 21-27 (Box 223)
    - 28-40 (Box 224)
    - 41-52 (Box 225)
    - 53-60 (Box 226)
    - 61-79 (Box 227)
    - 80-95 (Box 228)
    - 96-120 (Box 229)
    - 121-150 (Box 230)
    - 151-180 (Box 231)
    - 181-216 (Box 232)
    - 217-259 (Box Unnumbered box)
    - Official correspondence (Box Unnumbered box)
  - Correspondence pertaining to appointments as Notary Public, 1913-1915 (Box 233)
- Subgroup 22. Marcus H. Holcomb, 1915-1921
  - T001245, 20.5 cubic feet
    - Numerical Files, 1915-1916
      - 1-13 (Box 234)
      - 14-26 (Box 235)
      - 27-34 (Box 236)
      - 35-42 (Box 237)
      - 43-52 (Box 238)
      - 53-58 (Box 239)
      - 59-75 (Box 240)
      - 76-91 (Box 241)
      - 92-113 (Box 242)
      - 114-134 (Box 243)
      - 135-166 (Box 244)
      - 167-199 (Box 245)
    - Numerical File 200 and Correspondence pertaining to appointments as Notary Public, 1916-1917 (Box 246)
      Unarranged.
    - Alphabetical card index
      - 1915-1916 (Box 247)
      - 1917-1919 (Box 247)
      - 1919-1921 (Box 247)
        - A-C (Box 247)
        - C-Z (Box 248)
    - Draft Files, 1918 (Box 248)
    - Numerical Files, 1917-1918
      - 1-13 (Box 249)
      - 13-22 (Box 250)
      - 23-35 (Box 251)
      - 36-46 (Box 252)
      - 47-64 (Box 253)
      - 65-80 (Apr) (Box 254)
      - 80-83 (Box 255)
      - 84-101 (Box 256)
      - 102-117 (Box 257)
      - 118-130 (Box 258)
      - 131-137 3/4 (Box 259)
      - 138-144 (Box 260)
      - 145 (Box 261)
      - 145-148 (Box 262)
      - 149-162 (Box 263)
      - 163-182 (Box 264)
      - 183-224 (Box 265)
      - 201 A-Z (Box 266)
    - Numerical Files, 1919-1920
      - 1-13 (Box 267)
      - 14-33 (Box 268)
      - 34-38 (Box 269)
      - 39-52 (Box 270)
      - 53, 1919-1920 (Box 271a)
      - 53, 1920 (Box 271b)
      - 54-59 (Box 272)
      - 60-77 (Box 273)
      - 78-87 (Box 274)
      - 88-110 (Box 275)
      - 111-134 (Box 276)
      - 134-158 (Box 277)
      - 159-192 (Box 278)
      - 193-223 (Box 279)
      - 224-245 (Box 280)
    - Federal Suffrage Amendment, Petitions to Gov. Marcus H. Holcomb, 1920
      Bound volumes of correspondence calling special session of the General Assembly to ratify the 19th amendment.
      - A-C (Box Vol. 1)
      - D-J (Box Vol. 2)
      - K-S (Box Vol. 3)
      - T-Z (Box Vol. 4)
      - Miscellaneous (Box Vol. 5)
  - 1993-084
    - Resolutions adopted at Conference of New England Governors, 1919 December 10 (Box shared box)
- Subgroup 23. Everett J. Lake, 1921-1923; T001241; 7 cubic feet
  - Alphabetical card index, 1921-1923 (Box 281)
  - Alphabetical index to Personal Files, 1921-1923 (Box 281)
  - Numerical Files, 1921-1923
    - 2-27 (Box 282)
    - 28-43 (Box 283)
    - 44-59 (Box 284)
    - 60-69 (Box 285)
    - 70-90 (Box 286)
    - 91-120 (Box 287)
    - 121-149 (Box 288)
    - 151-161 (Box 289)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 289)
  - Personal Files, 1921-1923
    Official correspondence on personnel and political matters.
    Grouped by subject of state agency name and filed numerically.
    - 1-20 (Box 290)
    - 22-36 (Box 291)
    - 37-52 (Box 292)
    - 53-71 (Box 293)
    - 72-84 (Box 293)
      81, 83, 84 belong to Gov. Templeton.
- Subgroup 24. Charles A. Templeton, 1923-1925; T001240; 6.5 cubic feet
  - Alphabetical card index, 1923-1925 (Box 281)
  - Numerical Files, 1923-1925
    - 4-10 (Box 295)
    - 11-16 (Box 296)
    - 17-21 (Box 297)
    - 22-30 (Box 298)
    - 31-41 (Box 299)
    - 42-50 (Box 300)
    - 50-51 (Box 301)
    - 52-58 (Box 302)
    - 59-65 (Box 303)
    - 67-70 (Box 304)
    - 71-89 (Box 305)
    - 90-97 (Box 306)
    - 98-103 (Box 307)
- Subgroup 25. John H. Trumbull, 1925-1931
  Inventory of John H. Trumbull Gubernatorial Records
- Subgroup 26. Wilbur L. Cross, 1931-1939
  Inventory of Wilbur L. Cross Gubernatorial Records
- Subgroup 27. Raymond E. Baldwin, Jr., 1939-1941
  Inventory of Raymond E. Baldwin Gubernatorial Records
- Subgroup 28. Robert A. Hurley, 1941-1943
  Inventory of Robert A. Hurley Gubernatorial Records
- Subgroup 29. Raymond E. Baldwin, Jr., 1943-1946
- Subgroup 30. James L. McConaughy and James C. Shannon, 1947-1949
  Inventory of James L. McConaughy and James C. Shannon Gubernatorial Records
- Subgroup 31. Chester Bowles, 1949-1951
  Inventory of Chester Bowles Gubernatorial Records
- Subgroup 32. John Davis Lodge, 1951-1955
  Inventory of John Davis Lodge Gubernatorial Records
- Subgroup 33. Abraham Ribicoff, 1955-1961
  Inventory of Abraham Ribicoff Gubernatorial Records
- Subgroup 34. John Dempsey, 1961-1971
  Inventory of John Dempsey Gubernatorial Records
- Subgroup 35. Thomas J. Meskill, 1971-1975
  Inventory of Thomas J. Meskill Gubernatorial Records
- Subgroup 36. Ella T. Grasso, 1971-1980
  Inventory of Ella Grasso Gubernatorial Records
- Subgroup 37. William A. O'Neill, 1980-1991
  Inventory of William A. O'Neill Gubernatorial Records
- Subgroup 38. Lowell P. Weicker, 1990-1994
  Inventory of Lowell P. Weicker Gubernatorial Records
- Subgroup 39. John G. Rowland, 1995-2004
  Records of Gov. Rowland are being processed. Contact State Archives staff for assistance.
- Subgroup 40. M. Jodi Rell, 2004-2011
  Records of Gov. Rell have not been processed. Contact State Archives staff for assistance.
- Subgroup 41. Dannel P. Malloy, 2011-2015
  Records of Gov. Malloy have not been processed. Contact State Archives staff for assistance.